I have been practicing this for the whole morning,
so I hope it got it ... correct.
Uh,
this is my second time in Taipei and my first
iPlayground
and I thank the organizers for inviting me.
So I heard that the way to the heart of the
Taiwanese audience is through food.
So I hope you all had some good breakfast in
the morning because for the next 40 minutes
we are only going to talk about agents.
So my talk is about four agents and by agents.
I have divided into two stories.
The first is the inspiring part of building
in public so you can be inspired and go back
home and do a lot of open source work.
And the second part is on the technicals on
how I was able to get the agents to do a lot
of work for me,
still under my name.
And in 2026,
we use the agents,
we are not only working on the terminal by ourselves,
but we are also building tools for the developers
that are using these agents to use
the AI tools.
So before I start my presentation,
the whole presentation is made with Fable 5
in Claude Code with the translations and animations
and Codex 5.6 with this computer use to verify
everything.
So if you find me saying you are absolutely right,
you know where that is coming from.
So a bit of introduction about myself.
I worked with Apple Cupertino and the voice
controller and the Mac OS CD team,
and I worked with startups that went on to
become Apple Design Award finalist.
Last year I worked with Alex Sidebar,
which was cursor for Xcode and got acquired by OpenAI.
And right now I work for Rork,
where I manage the App Store and the Android
Publishing as well as the iOS app.
I have been a consistent speaker in different cities.
I was invited for iPlayground to talk about
building in public,
which unfortunately did not happen.
But I'm very happy to kind of have the same
talk and back on the stage again.
Back in 2019,
I won the WWDC Scholarship,
which kind of changed my trajectory of my life
because after going to DubDub
and meeting the developers there,
I started building in public.
And later,
after almost seven years,
earlier this year I was recognized as a community
leader at WWDC,
and you can see me at the corner there.
And everything in this talk is about building
in public and how I got the recognition from
the open source work I do and the community
building efforts.
I heard that MBTI is very popular in Taiwan.
So I wanted to mention that when you see me
on stage or when you're talking to me at the conference,
I'm actually an ENTJ.
But
I'm actually an INFP.
Like I would rather enjoy the midnight marina
in Singapore and enjoy the moments there.
And
I realized that posting online for me is much,
much easier than talking to people in real life.
And I made sure that I took full advantage of it.
And that's how I got to be known as the App Strore Connect
CLI guy.
I created the CLI six ... months ago,
and I feel like I've already aged a year in this time.
And the motivation behind this was
the App Store Connect website.
You already know the motivation.
I was so tired of this ...
Looking at the spinner when I working with the website
So I wanted Claude Code,
Codex,
Cursor,
all the agents out there to just use the like
I don't like skip the manual tapping around
and just say that for builds,
localization,
screenshots,
metadata,
upload,
everything is from a CLI.
So I can go and back and enjoy my life.
And this was possible because App Stroe Connect has an API.
So at the same time,
I was working for a client and they would send
me a lot of feedback on TestFlight.
I was very lazy to open the App Stroe Connect website
or go to the Xcode organizer.
I haven't opened Xcode in a long while.
So what I would do is I got to know about this endpoint.
Fastlane did not have this at the point when
I was creating it,
and there was a craz(y) of CLI in January.
So what I did was create a very small CLI which
would take the webhook,
like every time there's a new endpoint,
give it to Claude,
and then create a PR.
I wanted to create an automation loop.
And I wanted this to be AI native from day
one because I have not written a single line
of code in the past two years.
And while I'm proud to say that,
I feel like this is how we are going into this
world of agentic coding.
So back in January,
uh a popular AI tool gave me $25,000 in credits,
and I had access to the latest GPT and Claude models,
and I really wanted to do something for the
betterment of the iOS community and not worry
about tokens at all.
So at that time I started working with a model,
a MiniMax model,
which is a very nice fast model.
And then I also learned a bit of Mandarin in between.
And what I realized is that it said you should
not create the CLI in Swift and write it in Go itself,
which was very difficult for me because as
iOS developers,
we are just so used to writing code in Swift.
It gave me the reasons that it's a single binary,
it is cross-platform,
you have the fast builds,
a standard library,
and it is very easy to distribute via homebrew
and then or do uh let's say work on Linux
and Windows as well.
And the biggest inspiration for me was the
GitHub CLI because it's uh open sourced and
I realized that it was written pre-AI,
so they have actually worked very hard and
beautifully architected it.
And whenever I had any issues in the architecture side,
I would just ask my agents to reference it.
And if you keep my CLI and the GitHub CLI side by side,
you will see a lot of things in common.
But one thing that the MiniMax model told me
is that will you actually build it?
Because the ideas are cheap,
execution is everything.
You know how to use Claude Code to write,
help you write Go,
even if you don't know the language,
there's a market gap because FastLane does
not cover everything that App Stroe Connect has to provide.
So,
where do you start?
as
something who has been building in public,
I decided to just create a very small CLI with
one endpoint and then ask my Twitter audience,
would you actually want to use it?
And at the same time,
I realized that there's another platform called
as Threads where I can start posting.
And in the past few days,
I have realized that a lot of Taiwanese are on Threads.
So who all are on Threads here?
A lot of people.
So when I would post on X or Threads,
I would get very little response,
and but I still kept going because I was creating
it for myself.
I would start doing daily releases,
add small endpoints here and there,
and see what people would want,
and then there was still not much response,
but it became more than a weekend project.
But one of the tweets went very viral,
where I said that's one of the biggest releases,
and it covers the whole entire App Store flow.
And that tweet went viral,
got 100,000 views,
and then at that time I realized that the iOS
community has kind of noticed my work.
And in mid of February,
one of the founders of a huge company who ships
their SDKs to billions of devices on iPhone,
they told me that they personally use my CLI
and would want to replace Fastlane with my CLI.
So at that time I was like,
okay,
I have dragged something and I really want
to take it further.
And even my friend,
my close friend who now works in the Codex team,
he would hype everything I would talk about
and then post it and say that this is my mind is blown.
And then I realized another friend,
they would say,
bookmark this tweet if you are building for iOS app.
Nobody
tells you how difficult it is to do the App Store
submission.
So I got kind of a very small fan following
in the iOS community.
At that time,
I was like,
okay,
let's just cover everything that the App Store has to offer,
and I covered all the 1200 endpoints.
I was able to do it in less than a week.
I will talk about the technicals later.
And at this point,
I was like,
I would not renew the contract that I was working
on and then go full-time on this.
But then
I quit my client,
I was earning $15,000 a month,
and I went to $25
for sponsorship.
So I gave myself a month on how the CLI works out,
gave a big bet on this.
And even health-wise,
I gained like six,
seven kgs in two months because I was so addicted
to token maxing,
uh,
working till seven or eight in the morning.
And somehow next month,
uh random morning,
a startup called as Rork gave me $1,000 a month
as uh uh for uh GitHub sponsorship,
and it felt because they were already using
the CLI in their pipeline and they wanted to
pay it forward.
So it felt like somebody is literally paying
uh for me to maintain this.
And at the same time,
uh Claude started their open source program.
The main thing was that they would say that
if you have substantial uh impact in the community
and you have 5,000 stars on your repo,
you can apply.
At that time,
I only had two uh 2,500,
but I still went and applied,
and I was fortunate enough to get six months
of the pro plan or the max plan.
And at the same time,
OpenAI did something very similar.
So I had now two plans,
and in March itself,
I stopped paying for any subscriptions.
Like all of the work that I'm doing is now
funded by these two frontier labs.
And the biggest thing that I still cannot believe
is being on the OpenAI's Codex website.
So if you they have a page for building for iOS,
and they mention how to you can build the app for iOS,
and they mention the distribution stack where
for UI you have SwiftUI,
for working with Xcode,
you have uh XcodeBuildMCP,
and for distribution tooling,
you have App Store Connect CLI with and they
mentioned keep your agents fully in the loop
and send your app directly to the app store.
So at this point,
I was like,
if there are millions of codex users who can
naturally work and understand my CLI,
I can take it now forward.
I don't know what the future of the CLI was,
but I was still enjoying the validation that
I was getting.
And every day I would wake up and see a lot
of folks tagging me that this CLI has changed
their life.
I got more sponsorship at this point,
and I would do a lot of daily releases.
At the same time,
my friend again,
Thomas,
he would baited me into creating a new app.
He said,
Told me that you are creating a CLI.
Why don't you just create an App Store client on top of it?
So I was like,
I would just do it.
I have a lot of tokens at this point.
And at the same day,
I started getting a lot of job offers and acquisition
calls,
and I decided to do a stable release.
I would work very hard 10-15 hours to clean
up the slop code,
all the experimental thing I did,
and did a 1.0 release.
I had uh dozens of contributors who would work on it.
The issues were written by AI,
by their agents,
and my agent would then see their agents work
and then work on it.
And it literally
felt like we are just watching a movie of agents
talking to the agents.
I created something that was inspired by uh WWDC,
where you have a wall of apps,
so people who contribute their apps would,
if they use the CLI,
they would go and contribute on this wall of apps,
so that it's just a nice feeling.
And in the end,
I realized why this building in public matters
because all the work that I got in the past
few years have this has been from GitHub,
and I realized my GitHub has become my resume.
And the biggest motivation for this was because
I hate LeetCode.
I just did not want to do LeetCode at all,
and I realized that GitHub can be a way to
have employment as well.
So after two months,
I was able to get 14 job opportunities where
I did not apply,
but I got reached out on Twitter and LinkedIn.
Uh some from the Frontier Labs.
I got three acquisition offers for the CLI,
which is very funny because it is MIT licensed.
They could have just clicked on the fork button,
but they wanted to buy it instead.
And in the end,
I took an Acquihire where I sold the CLI uh
for cash and then joined the team full-time,
uh,
which is my first full-time job after seven years.
And I was very hell-bent on keeping it MIT
licensed because uh this was not possible because
of all the dozens of contributors from all
around the world.
I was calculating in the morning,
and there were like ... people,
uh,
developers from 30 countries have contributed this CLI,
and I really did not want to,
I wanted to ship the same way and keep it open
source that we all can take benefit from it.
So from the burning room where I was just earning $25
a month,
I was now I was able to be more financially
secure and earn a decent San Francisco salary.
And my job went from creating the CLI to kind
of maintaining the CLI.
And I read this quote on threats recently.
When the water arrives,
the channel forms.
I did not want to force my way into like being
desperate on what I want to do with the CLI,
but just wait for the time.
I just trusted the process.
I kept building every single day and promoting
my work without knowing what the
like expecting the destination it,
and in the end,
there are almost a hundred thousand developers
who are using this CLI.
Just give me a second.
大家還醒著嗎？
So are you all still awake?
Because for the first part we talked about
the inspiration,
and in the second part we talk about the technicals
and how you can create an AI tool that can
maintain itself.
Because I realize at this point I am spending
an hour a week,
less than an hour a week maintaining it,
but I'm still shipping at the same speed that
I was doing it before.
So in the beginning,
I realized that I have become a prompt engineer.
I was not an iOS engineer or anything.
I have become I would just write prompts and
then review the agent‘s code,
realize that the man and then manage the agents
as a manager.
I would write the rules.
I realized I was running the same checklist
every single day where I would say a daily
loop of please go through the PR comments and
loop through until it's green.
If somebody would send a issue,
like please triage it,
if they would send a PR,
please fix it,
see how it is working or not.
And when everything is green,
I would say please create a new release.
And I felt like I have become a cron job or
a GitHub action with feelings as a human.
And I wanted to change this.
So I was like,
okay,
what can I do with this new AI world that can
help me maintain on its own?
So to give you an idea,
this uh uh repository has almost 600,000 lines of code.
Lines of code is a bad metric,
but the idea is that I wanted to give an idea
if I can create half a million lines of code
in a few months.
Why
is it not breaking so much?
Like this is a question that I would get asked a lot.
And the biggest reason for this was I did a
lot of test-driven development.
Every endpoint would get a test,
any regressions that the people would face,
I would have issues.
And I wanted a way that the agents can verify
their own work as much as they can without
me in the process at all.
And this led to having a lot of rules.
I started with the basics where I had a normal
agents.md file where all the rules lived.
Every agent would read it,
but I also want it to be self-improving,
which means that for any change that felt very
weird or something that could have been or
is very repeatable or redundant,
I would ask the agent would automatically add
it as a new rule.
So I would not write the rules myself.
I wanted the agents to write the rules for themselves,
and then every week I would review if it is
working well or if it is not working well.
Few of the rules in the beginning,
which is kind of redundant now,
which is how good the models are.
I would want it to reproduce the issue first,
do not take any shortcuts,
never bypass any checks because the models
in the beginning would love to do this and
be honest about the pre-existing issues that
they were facing.
So do not delete a test just because you want
to have that green check.
And one thing that I learned was sosumi.ai,
which can bypass uh the Apple JavaScript,
so I can get the docs directly if the open
API schema did not provide it for App Store Connect.
And the Agents.md kind of grew every month
with every release.
New incident would get added to each time,
and then I realized that I needed a bit of
refactor because we moved from agents.md to
something called as skills because we are still
in a ... hype cycle.
So the refactor was also done by the agents themselves.
I wanted something uh that the agents
I wanted the skills to be in a way that is
not invoked manually by the agents,
but I can create automations on top of it.
So all these skills that I created were automations
for each and that I can run and then manually
do it on my Mac mini.
I started with a very small one,
which was review the wall of app PRs.
I started as untrusted until proven,
which means I would just take it sounds very bad,
but I would take every PR that somebody would
put as a prompt injection.
I wanted to make sure that all the lines that
they have added,
which is five lines are ... can be verified.
It's Apple links,
it would go,
the agents would go to the link and cross-verify
the store page and then see the app icon as
well and if it matches the app as well or not.
I was I just wanted to make sure that uh all
the PRs that are on the wall of apps were verified
for each of the lines.
Because uh for this skill,
I gave it the
autonomy to actually merge on its own.
The second was triaging the issues that I faced,
all of them were from external contributors.
I would want to reproduce the issues and label
them like uh easy,
medium,
or high,
or if it is P0 or P1 and P2,
because when I was doing the automations,
I would want them to uh because when I have
like let's say five to ten PRs,
I want the agents to figure out what's more
important at that time so that if it is a P0 issue,
I would want the automation to just do a new
release at the same time versus uh P2 that
can be okay uh for uh doing it later on.
So if there's any unclear evidence,
I would just put as a lower priority and state
the assumptions.
And everything was something that I'm at this
point trust the agents as well because when
I cross-verify,
I'm very sure that they're doing a good work.
It was very similar for the external contributions
I get as a PR.
Like in the morning,
two hours ago,
I did a new release.
Uh the agents did a new release,
and I realized that uh that the PR that I got
from the external contributor was kind of incomplete.
So my agent would review the work and then
uh go through,
use my ASC API key to find uh what was missing
and then patch the PR well.
And because that was the evidence-first review I wanted,
like whatever they are submitting is actually
what the direction was good,
but it wasn't what I would want as the standard
to maintain because in the beginning I was
okay vibe coding this CLI,
uh,
but as I have more uh number of developers
who are actually dependent on it for their
daily workflow,
I just cannot have any mistakes done by agents
when I'm not the one reviewing them.
Finally,
I had a release ASC CLI which is for creating
the release itself,
which does an end-to-end test,
gets all the issues and PRs that were merged,
and make sure because it gets a new fresh context,
so it has a new uh fresh eyes on seeing all
the work that it did.
It checks daily for a new release and for any
patch or minor releases it does on its own.
For major releases,
I I'm still in the loop as a human.
It would download the binary and run the code
sign to see if nothing has been uh compromised
and then run all the new uh commands or anything
that was added to make sure that the whole
CLI can be uh used for production work.
And lastly,
a skill for updating the skill file.
So I would have a separate repo to make sure
that there's no drift in the command.
So if any external developers are using the skills,
they can use the the up-to-date skill.
So I was I tried as much as I can to use cloud
agents for this.
So each agent would get my ASC API key,
uh
separate one that would be in the environment secrets,
and I also created a throwaway app for testing,
just for testing.
It can do,
uh it can send it to waiting for review,
it can send for subscriptions.
I even gave it the autonomy to create expert projects.
For example,
when I was testing the App Clips,
I did not have any apps with App Clips.
So it would create a new app and add App Clips,
try it to submit to the App Store and see the
whole process is working or not.
So this was a dear loop I wanted,
which I can run for a lot of the agents without
me in the loop.
Because I realized that my user is the agent.
I don't know.
I have talked to a lot of developers,
but I haven't found anybody who's actually
typing the commands in the terminal themselves.
So my user,
I so what I would do is ask the agent,
do you think if you have to use something like this,
would you be able like be okay using this?
And then I would ask the same question to both
Codex and Claude because I realize these two
models would have different opinions.
So I would take both of the opinions and then
uh form the commands or anything that I'm working on.
And this is kind of the way I have developed
for developing AI tools.
So because in the end,
the AI tools are created for the agent themselves.
For example,
this is an issue on the repo where Cursor created
an issue where it went through the fastlane repo,
found an issue
where we can fix it in our CLI itself,
and then it would go through and write the whole
spec itself,
summarize,
find the problem,
the link,
and the proposal,
and then it would use my name and say,
please implement this end-to-end.
Then the Cursor cloud agent would implement it,
and then overnight it would create and reproduce
everything,
and
uh
it says the rudrankriyam and then it's a fixed in 5.30,
but it is actually the agent.
So even if it says my name,
it is still cursor who did the whole implementation.
And I would in the beginning run a lot of agents
6-7 overnight,
where I would brainstorm with the first agent
and it would create different cloud agents,
and in the morning I would wake up to 5-10
PRs ready to review,
which is already tested on my live production data.
So I ended up creating something called a factory
of agents where I have wall of apps that run
twice a day,
the skill drift daily for the issue,
hygiene daily,
bug scanner releases,
everything runs uh daily.
And I did not want it to have something that's
very technical,
or very complicated system,
just something that I can reuse with what Claude
or Codex offers or Cursor offers,
what the automation offers.
So I don't have to spend much time.
Like my main idea after selling the CLI was
not to spend much more time on it.
And in the end,
I was able to create an autonomous release
cycle where the new submission would go through
the diff,
find the PR.
If the diff was clean,
merge everything,
see the I can sometimes have to find the SHA is wrong,
then redo the release cycle again,
check for everything is good.
So it felt like I had many agents just to make
sure that the release is something I can fully trust.
And last month there was a time when Codex
did a release overnight with a huge line of PRs,
I think 16 PRs,
and I woke up in the morning at the same time
as others reading the release notes.
And it felt very cool on surface,
but I realized that I felt like a stranger
to my own product because I was reading the
release notes without knowing what happened overnight.
So for all the small patches or minor patches,
I make sure that it is automated for anything
that's major now.
I am sure that I'm involved,
so it still feels like even though because
it is still using my name when it's doing a release,
so I want to be in the loop.
And finally,
one thing I want to share is something I have
discovered called as agentception.
So last WWDC I was talking to a lot of developers
and they mentioned that Claude does not work
well with the CLI,
and I had no idea how to debug that.
So what I did was because even at work we use
Claude models as the default one.
So I could I was going to the tool calls and
realized that it is doing a lot of
hallucinated tool calls,
and I don't know how to fix it.
So I added analytics to understand how the
users are using it.
It's anonymous,
there's no there's no confidential data that
is being sent,
no app ID,
no arguments,
just the command that is being invoked.
And in the end,
I realized over the past month that the  Claude
models had two times more errors than Codex.
And this was very fascinating for me because
Claude models,
this was not tested on Fable 5,
I'm sure Fable 5 would do better.
But Claude models would were so overconfident
that they would just make up the commands themselves
and then later realize that okay,
they did something wrong,
and then search the CLI and try to find it.
But Codex was much slower,
more wise.
It would use the dash dash help for each of
the commands and then say that okay,
this is the command that it should use,
and then be more accurate,
even though it takes a bit more time.
So I realized I cannot fix the model itself,
but I can fix my CLI.
So something I think I came up with as when
I was showering is I can take all the hallucinated
commands and add it as a type alias.
So whenever Claude would do the wrong uh hallucinated
command,
that would actually point to the actual command.
And I felt that was very cool because in the end,
I was able to create an autonomous loop for
this as well.
Every day it reads the analytics,
adds any type alias that it should add,
fixes any error messages or any description
that it should do,
and then open PR.
And then the release cycle release automation
would pick up these changes and then create
an autonomous loop where I can say that it
is kind of a self-improving CLI that is getting
better every day.
And with this,
I was able to do 186 releases over six months,
which is almost one a day.
Zero open issues,
zero open PRs right now, this morning,
and I realize at this point I can have the
agents maintain the product and not me,
even though I realize that I have to be in
the loop just to cross-verify the work that
it's doing is well or not.
And the way that we're exploiting with the models,
I don't think I even have to do that anymore.
So,
how do you even start?
So the first question that I realized is just
ask your model.
If you're using Codex,
just ask Codex.
Start small,
ask,
go,
ask it to go through your local Codex chats
or your local Claude chats and what you can automate.
Have some daily tasks that you can automate.
Like one thing I realized is at work is that
I would miss a lot of the work that somebody
would tag me on.
So every morning I have forgotten work skill
that would run and go through my Slack and
then debrief me what went wrong,
and I would have the same for my PR that I would do.
The automation should take care of itself at
a point where I'm very confident.
And I now have been experimenting with something
called as uh automation on the top of the automation,
which means that it would go through all the
automations that ran and check which ones were
doing well and which were not doing well and
how to improve that as well.
So,
my role,
as Gyuri said yesterday in her talk,
is that I'm now something who is maintaining
the direction of the CLI or the AI tools that
I'm creating and not worrying about the small
stuff that we used to worry about earlier.
And with that,
I'm done with my talk.
What?
Did the agents take over my slides?
So,
what is this one more thing?
I realized I can extend this idea to iOS development
as well.
Uh,
because last week,
just a few days ago,
we released an iOS app which runs an app,
the actual native app,
inside the native app.
And from the phone itself,
you can do the whole App Store publishing.
And I'm very proud to do this using the agents,
even though I say that I did it.
So you can have the build screenshots,
metadata,
everything from the phone itself.
And the idea of agentception is something
I could apply here as well with something using
called as agent device,
which can run the automation on my iPhone and
then verify everything that's it is being done.
It is a bit slow when you're doing the UI testing,
but it's something that I wanted.
So one example that I did was I was brainstorming
everything that I wanted with the main orchestrator
agent.
Orchestrator sounds very fancy,
but just a mean agent,
and then ask it to spawn.
Instead of asking it to spawn sub-agents,
I asked it to spawn different threads per feature
because I realized that the main each.. the main
thread can also message the different threads.
So it was it would run the app on my phone,
take the screenshot,
keep the evidence,
look at the screenshots,
and see if anything is going wrong or not.
And then if it found any bad code,
any slop,
it would the main orchestrator agent would
fix it and it would write such good prompts
that I cannot even think about in this life.
It would get uh go through the
human interface guidelines,
see if a button is like let's say
32 points,
and then ask it to fix it.
And one of the cool things was that this recovery
agent that I have grayed out is something that
it wanted to uh uh work on,
and then it's like this is something that's
not achievable in this release,
so we are going to stop it and focus on the
other ones that we have.
And in the end,
I was able to run it for seven hours straight
with GPT-5.6 sold running on my iPhone,
and it almost gave me perfect work where I
had to fix the the some changes or polish my
work for one hour,
and the best part was during the seven hours
I was able to play my PlayStation straight,
even though I was the one who delivered the work.
And the best part of all of this is the models Fable 5,
Opus 5,
GPT 5.6,
even Kimi K3 is the worst that we will ever get,
and because we still have five months in this uh year.
Like this chart shows how the length of the
task the AI agents can do is growing every every month,
and the quality is also increasing,
just not the time itself.
And for me,
personally,
my deadline for making the most out of all
these agents is November 19th,
because that matter that date really matters
for me because I want to play GTA 6 as much
as I can without worrying about uh the agents
working for me,
and it's still under my name.
And with that,
I finished my talk.
Uh,
you can find me on Twitter and thread with my name,
and I am very active there to talk a lot about
everything that I'm talking about,
share all the things that I can with that, 謝謝.